[Music]
54321 a steady bleed answer the phone
after this there will be only one Victor
an excellent fight and you matter attack
the objective behind you defended one
mystery the near enemy teleporter
detected Josh enemy teleporter destroyed
eliminate the target enemy turret ahead
your enemy turrets destroyed even here I
feel a knob cast for work farewell
faster than site who fate smiled upon me
flow like water gender here Kenji is
with you get out of there move hello
honor the Fallen how I enemies a week
this is our chance I am certain of it I
am defending I am healed I am ready I am
taking the objective join me ambala find
peace I've found the teleporter I move
to strike I need armor I learned that
for my brother I move to strike I need
armor I need a healing i need help i
need a shield I return to the fight I
still have much to learn I understand i
will make use of this i will try go
enemies where they do not expect I will
not falter I will not waste this chance
I'm fortunate for you I'm with you it is
not too late to change your course
brother it comes to this do not falter
it is an honor it was nothing catch ago
hua tera mera toh ningun lado torrini
kerala Kentucky lewisham cargo wha
Gotama Shiva Kim como tu mera raja
organized oh ahora la coruna laga cocalo
make your city sin on Eureka yosh its
demo koi orange Peru she also that I
amino acids in you are now atole Katie
Maurice and mega oh yes hiya scrub oak
ave naugatuck show head luchador bouquet
no horn re-sing yo toe sha kai jin let's
dye them so no ta loka my god how much
your mother Moyer you a Warriner then
Kosuke honky omitted in your citizen yo
yo la Mara Mara can I touch cavy or even
more go young son me it's
either Jin Jeong Subin Hari a fella
Cristiano hasta la cocina kogarah
terminando me neostem oh no you act even
send a new much more josh is at the
corner I wanna store she has coming
orders Your Majesty money poker up
feeling icky you're silly scanner stoner
ooh la la a las casas it's your kitty
none of us you what any other real
muezzin I only nagar covino garage we're
still gonna alligatoah yoga Colonel Ted
oka you're just my style just setting
from here that's my soul of ease keep
the payload emotion know yourself in the
face of death let us hope for different
outcome life and death balanced on the
edge of my blade like cutting through
silk many an hour of my misspent youth
were passed here let's finish this
quickly measure twice cut once my aim is
unerring my blade is ready to be
unleashed my skills improve my spirit
grows strong my task is not complete my
ultimate is ready on my way how enemies
return our enemies have the upper hand
for now let us turn the tables our point
is under attack let us welcome our
guests press the attack push the payload
push Ford revenge takes only one who
seeks it set up here simple flavor beer
airy so this is what has become of you
happy d something for my trouble stand
together die together stop the payload
swift as the wind thank you
what do you dream not mine that was
another life the dragon and I are one so
was your dream not mine that was another
life the advantage is mine the borrowed
Rose please conclusion we must attack
the enemy teleporter is no longer
concerned the payload is moving stop it
the payroll is topped and here I thought
we had a plan the payload moves we must
keep it safe the objective is mine be
quick about it the winds of deaths are
strong there is no time to dwell in the
past now we fight sync up on your
actions time is against us press on to
know yourself is to be a piece very well
victories road near defend watch
yourself we are losing the objective
push them back we must press our
advantage and see is thick tree we need
to stop the payload converge upon it we
shall see brother we will fight again
well struck What's Wrong handle don't
you recognize me you are only human you
are worthy
[Music]
you